(Howard:)I wouldn't be the sidekick.
You'd be the sidekick.
(Raj:)Rat-Man is nobody's sidekick.
(Howard:)Leonard, settle this.
(Howard:)Of the two of us, who's
the obvious sidekick?
(Raj:)Yeah, Leonard, who?
(Leonard:)12 years after high school,
and I'm still at the nerd table.
(Sheldon:)Aren't you slicing that
man's brain a little too thin?
(Amy:)It's too thin if I were making
(Amy:)a foot-long brain sandwich
at Quiznos.
(Amy:)For examination under a two-
photon microscope, it's fine.
(Sheldon:)Well, you're the expert.
(Sheldon:)If the correct way to do it
is the wrong way, then I yield.
(Amy:)Very well.
(Amy:)If you die and donate
your body to science,
(Amy:)I promise to slice your brain
like Canadian bacon.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Amy:)Now, if you'll
excuse me,
(Amy:)I have to take my temperature.